Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC)
approximately 1865-2015
Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College
152 cubic feet (152 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Clippings, biographical information forms, correspondence, articles, and other items gathered by the Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College (AAVC) on women who attended the college from 1865-1942 and 1951-1958. The collection includes material on graduates, non-graduates, Special Students and Preparatory Students.
Administrative History
The Associated Alumnae of Vassar College (AAVC) was formed in 1871. The name was changed in 1970 to Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College to reflect the institution's acceptance of male students. It has always been an independent organization, rather than a department of Vassar College. The purposes of the AAVC include raising money for scholarships, providing a network of support for students after graduation, and enabling the exchange of information between the college and its graduates.
Scope and Content Note
Clippings, biographical information forms, correspondence, articles, and other items gathered by the Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College (AAVC) on women who attended the college from 1865-1942 and 1951-1958. The collection includes material on graduates, non-graduates, Special Students and Preparatory Students. Note: The container list for this collection does not constitute a complete alumnae/i listing; not every graduate is represented.
Access
Files from members of the Class of 1931 and later are currently closed to research. The rest of this collection is open for research according to the regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library without any additional restrictions.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Alumni and alumnae
Subjects:
Women college graduates; Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Students and Alumnae/i
Encoding Information
Encoded by Gretchen Maslin and Laura Streett, 2013-2014.
Updated by Zachary Bodnar and Miranda Villesvik, 2017.
Updated by Isabel Bielat, 2018.
Last updated by Emma Gronbeck, October 2024.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College in 2008, 2015, 2018, and 2021.
Accruals
Accruals are expected every 5-10 years.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by class year, then alphabetically by last name. Note: some students were assigned a class year, or chose to identify with a specific class, regardless of when or if they actually graduated.
Series List
  1865— 1866— 1867— 1868— 1869— 1870— 1871— 1872— 1873— 1874— 1875— 1876
  1877— 1878— 1879— 1880— 1881— 1882— 1883— 1884— 1885— 1886— 1887— 1888
  1889— 1890— 1891— 1892— 1893— 1894— 1895— 1896— 1897— 1898— 1899— 1900
  1901— 1902— 1903— 1904— 1905— 1906— 1907— 1908— 1909— 1910— 1911— 1912
  1913— 1914— 1915— 1916— 1917— 1918— 1919— 1920— 1921— 1922— 1923— 1924
  1925— 1926— 1927— 1928— 1929— 1930— 1931— 1932— 1933— 1934— 1935— 1936
  1937— 1938-1942— 1951-1958
Container List
- Class of 1865
  - Baker, Mary Ellen (Box 1)
  - Boardman, Ellen D. (Box 1)
  - Coe, Mary Augusta (Box 1)
  - Davis, Emma Parker (Box 1)
  - Gardner, Kate (Box 1)
  - Glass, Margaret E. (Box 1)
  - Holt, Eliza (Box 1)
  - Maltby, Elizabeth (Box 1)
  - Metcalf, Elizabeth (Box 1)
  - Morrison, Alice (Box 1)
  - Noyes, Elizabeth Coles (Box 1)
  - Pierson, Ellen C. (Box 1)
  - Taylor, Anna (Box 1)
  - Smith, Cynthia Jane (Box 1)
  - Tutwiler, Julia Strudwick (Box 1)
- Class of 1866
  - Frost, Mary Louise (Box 1)
  - Griggs, Harriet Barnes (Box 1)
  - Treadwell, Isabelle A. (Box 1)
- Class of 1867
  - Camp, Harriette Anne (Box 1)
  - Case, Helen Adeline (Box 1)
  - Cunningham, Susan (Box 1)
  - Davies, Margaret Louise (Box 1)
  - Denny, Emily Davies (Box 1)
  - Derby, Florence C. (Box 1)
  - Dickinson, Maria L. (Box 1)
  - French, Alice (Box 1)
  - Fuller, Kate (Box 1)
  - Geiger, Elizabeth L. (Box 1)
  - Goodale, Estelle Jeanne (Box 1)
  - Green, Isabella T. (Box 1)
  - Harmon, Clara (Box 1)
  - Harmon, Martha Loomis (Box 1)
  - Hawley, Rebecca de R. (Box 1)
  - Jayne, Emma Lois (Box 1)
  - Miller, Frances Parsons (Box 1)
  - Norton, Margaret Louise (Box 1)
  - Olmsted, Fannie Pardee (Box 1)
  - Pendleton, Elizabeth P. (Box 1)
  - Porter, Alice Maynard (Box 1)
  - Spaulding, Clara L. (Box 1)
  - Standring, Emma Frances (Box 1)
  - Thomas, Zadora G. (Box 1)
  - Warner, Harriette A. (Box 1)
  - Woodward, Helen D. (Box 1)
- Class of 1868
  - Avery, Mary L. (Box 1)
  - Beckwith, Elizabeth R. (Box 1)
  - Carter, Isabella (Box 1)
  - Corbit, Mary Cogwill (Box 1)
  - Cornell, Mary Emily (Box 1)
  - Doubleday, Mary (Box 1)
  - Ely, Achsah M. (Box 1)
  - Evans, Anne M. (Box 1)
  - Fanton, Ann Augusta (Box 1)
  - Frothingham, Gertrude (Box 1)
  - Glazier, Sarah M. (Box 1)
  - Glover, Clara E. (Box 1)
  - Herrick, Sara J. (Box 1)
  - Hoyt, Maria L. (Box 1)
  - Leland, Cornelia P. (Box 1)
  - Maguire, Fanny Louisa (Box 1)
  - Parsons, Louise F. (Box 1)
  - Platt, Harriet Browne (Box 1)
  - Rhoades, Mary P. (Box 1)
  - Stagg, Maria (Box 1)
  - Starr, Sarah (Box 1)
  - Stewart, Hannah M. (Box 1)
  - Stillwell, Julia D. (Box 1)
  - Stoddard, Sarah T. (Box 1)
  - Storke, Helen L. (Box 1)
  - Theaker, Margaret E. (Box 1)
  - Warner, Martha S. (Box 1)
  - Whitney, Mary W. (Box 1)
  - Wilkinson, Jane H. (Box 1)
- Class of 1869
  - Alexander, Margaret S. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Lillie (Box 1)
  - Barnaby, Maria Eliza (Box 1)
  - Bagg, Sophia D. (Box 1)
  - Babcock, Ellen W. (Box 1)
  - Beers, Lily K. (Box 1)
  - Christie, Helen R. (Box 1)
  - Colby, Emma M. (Box 1)
  - Constant, Mary J. (Box 1)
  - Daniels, Sarah E. (Box 1)
  - De Clerq, Julia K. (Box 1)
  - De Golyer, Lilias A. (Box 1)
  - Gilbert, Mary L. (Box 1)
  - Harbottle, Cornelia Sophia (Box 1)
  - Herrick, Sara Jane (Box 1)
  - Holbrook, Mary Eugenia (Box 1)
  - Hubbard, Emma L. (Box 1)
  - Jones, Anna E. (Box 1)
  - Kelley, Helen Frances (Box 1)
  - Ladd, Christine (Box 1)
  - Liggett, Ella M. (Box 1)
  - Morrison, Katherine A. (Box 1)
  - Morris, Cara Bell (Box 1)
  - Middleditch, Sarah Helena (Box 1)
  - Maybury, Mary (Box 1)
  - Parsons, Mary Ella (Box 1)
  - Read, Rebecca Judson (Box 1)
  - Scofield, Ellie Gamble (Box 1)
  - Shove, Ellen Marian (Box 1)
  - Stewart, Helen W. (Box 1)
  - Strong, Belle A. (Box 1)
  - Talcott, Eliza S. (Box 1)
  - Talcott, Emeline Frances (Box 1)
  - Tolman, Emilie (Box 1)
  - Waddington, Pauline (Box 1)
  - White, J. Clara (Box 1)
  - Whitney, Anna Maria (Box 1)
- Class of 1870
  - Austin, Mary L. (Box 1)
  - Case, Frances E. (Box 1)
  - Chumar, Mary (Box 1)
  - Clark, Annie Maude (Box 1)
  - Clarke, Lepha N. (Box 1)
  - Coffin, Elizabeth R. (Box 1)
  - Crockett, Grace H. (Box 1)
  - Crowe, Viola R. (Box 1)
  - Crowell, Elizabeth O. (Box 1)
  - Denniston, Abbey Lyon (Box 1)
  - Denton, Jane A. (Box 1)
  - Demarest, Jeanie W. (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Caroline Morgan (Box 1)
  - Hatt, Annie I. (Box 1)
  - Higgins, Helen C. (Box 1)
  - Hoskins, Sarah E. (Box 1)
  - Hoyt, Annie E. (Box 1)
  - Hoyt, Frances (Box 1)
  - Huffman, Elba (Box 1)
  - Huntington, Jeannette P. (Box 1)
  - Huntington, Kate (Box 1)
  - McGraw, Georgiana (Box 1)
  - Mead, M. Gertrude (Box 1)
  - Merrick, Lillie (Box 1)
  - Mineah, Mary A. (Box 1)
  - Montague, Abby Talitha (Box 1)
  - Norris, Mary H. (Box 1)
  - Palmer, Harriet O. (Box 1)
  - Parker, Mary A. (Box 1)
  - Rice, Mary L. (Box 1)
  - Ritch, Cynthia W. (Box 1)
  - Robinson, Ella C. (Box 1)
  - Rushmore, Lucinda V. (Box 1)
  - Sampson, Sarah E. (Box 1)
  - Seeley, Kate A. (Box 1)
  - Skeel, Ellen A. (Box 1)
  - Smith, Deborah Collins (Box 1)
  - Storke, Sophia D. (Box 1)
  - Swallow, Ellen H. (Box 1)
  - Tash, Clara Stuart (Box 1)
  - Trumbull, Harriet (Box 1)
  - Williams, Mary Ann Maria (Box 1)
  - Woods, Amanda W. (Box 1)
- Class of 1871
  - Adams, Ida W. (Box 1)
  - Cleveland, Esther Maria (Box 1)
  - Earle, Mariana Mifflin (Box 1)
  - Esty, Amelai W. (Box 1)
  - Folsom, Ellen M. (Box 1)
  - Garnsey, Emma H. (Box 1)
  - Glover, Marie O. (Box 1)
  - Gross, Eva Hedges (Box 1)
  - Harper, Elizabeth F. (Box 1)
  - Hawks, Emma L. (Box 1)
  - Hileman, Dora (Box 1)
  - Hood, Bettie Turner (Box 1)
  - Hopper, Euphemia W. (Box 1)
  - House, Mary C. (Box 1)
  - Hughey, Eliza Teressa (Box 1)
  - Jewett, Kate G. (Box 1)
  - Kinkead, Annie Pearce (Box 1)
  - Ladew, Louise (Box 1)
  - Lewis, Sarah B. D. (Box 1)
  - Loveland, Kate A. (Box 1)
  - Lovell, Fannie Z. (Box 1)
  - Monks, Sarah P. (Box 1)
  - Nicoll, Mary S. (Box 1)
  - Parsons, Annette P. (Box 1)
  - Pennell, Mary (Box 1)
  - Raymond, Susan (Box 1)
  - Reeves, Mary T. (Box 1)
  - Rice, Emma Augusta (Box 1)
  - Rowe, Annie E. (Box 1)
  - Sage, Ella Florence (Box 1)
- Class of 1872
  - Alexander, Julia Bowles (Box 2)
  - Atwood, Mary Louise (Box 2)
  - Avery, Gertrude Arms (Box 2)
  - Baxter, Charlotte P. (Box 2)
  - Blackmar, Anna (Box 2)
  - Brace, Maria P. (Box 2)
  - Bradley, Jessie S. (Box 2)
  - Brayton, Mary (Box 2)
  - Burch, Katherine N. (Box 2)
  - Catlin, Ella Amelia (Box 2)
  - Clapp, Caroline (Box 2)
  - Corson, Ida (Box 2)
  - Crockett, Lucy E. (Box 2)
  - De Wolfe, Kate Finch (Box 2)
  - Dellicker, Julia Wildman (Box 2)
  - Dinsmoor, Alice (Box 2)
  - Eliot, Wilimena (Box 2)
  - Farwell, Abby (Box 2)
  - Foster, Alla W. (Box 2)
  - Gheen, Hettie Woodward (Box 2)
  - Godfrey, Annie Roberts (Box 2)
  - Gunn, Mary Gold (Box 2)
  - Hall, Agnes W. (Box 2)
  - Hancock, Ellen (Box 2)
  - Harrington, Harriet R. (Box 2)
  - Heale, Minnie A. (Box 2)
  - Hollister, Ella S. (Box 2)
  - Hopson, Annie Waterman (Box 2)
  - Jameson, Mary Sanders (Box 2)
  - Kirby, Elizabeth P. (Box 2)
  - Loomis, Mary A. (Box 2)
  - Manning, Helen Abbie (Box 2)
  - Rawson, Mary J. (Box 2)
  - Rollinson, Elizabeth S. (Box 2)
  - Rumsey, Amelia Vernon (Box 2)
  - Rumsey, Lillias J. (Box 2)
  - Rumsey, Martha Turner (Box 2)
  - Seelye, Alice D. (Box 2)
  - Semple, Pattie B. (Box 2)
  - Stem, Sarah M. (Box 2)
  - Taintor, Ruth Smith (Box 2)
  - Thornton, Hattie L. (Box 2)
  - Waldron, Martha M. (Box 2)
  - Wetmore, Alice M. (Box 2)
- Class of 1873
  - Abbott, Elizabeth O. (Box 2)
  - Angell, Isabel (Box 2)
  - Atkinson, Lucy Alice (Box 2)
  - Baker, Carrie Canfield (Box 2)
  - Bartlett, Anna A. (Box 2)
  - Beach, Jennie H. (Box 2)
  - Beardely, Emily Griffith (Box 2)
  - Beaver, Anna Wheaton (Box 2)
  - Bedell, Mary Sanderson (Box 2)
  - Bell, Julia E. (Box 2)
  - Birney, Alice Amelia (Box 2)
  - Brayton, Nannie J. (Box 2)
  - Brewer, Elizabeth H. (Box 2)
  - Chapin, Julia E. (Box 2)
  - Clark, Mrs. John B. (Box 2)
  - Corliss, Lucy F. (Box 2)
  - Croll, Amelia Doudel (Box 2)
  - Cutting, J. Harriet I. (Box 2)
  - Dana, Sarah S. (Box 2)
  - Durand, Frances E. (Box 2)
  - Gasper, Jennie Beach (Box 2)
  - Gerrish, Caroline M. (Box 2)
  - Griffith, Emily C. (Box 2)
  - Hale, Harriet Swinburne (Box 2)
  - Hiscock, Helen C. (Box 2)
  - Hoagland, Eliza (Box 2)
  - Hopson, Mary A. (Box 2)
  - Houghton, Elizabeth G. (Box 2)
  - Jessup, Lillian Jay (Box 2)
  - Keene, Julia Matilda (Box 2)
  - Kelley, Adelaide Skeel (Box 2)
  - Knowles, Cornelia (Box 2)
  - Kretjinger, Clara Wilson (Box 2)
  - Liggett, Frances C. (Box 2)
  - Lupton, Katherine M. (Box 2)
  - Marcher, Marie A. (Box 2)
  - Monroe, Mary (Box 2)
  - Moore, Felicia E. (Box 2)
  - Morss, Merilla T. (Box 2)
  - Noble, Harriet (Box 2)
  - Perry, M. Eva (Box 2)
  - Phelps, Anna R. (Box 2)
  - Pratt, Gertrude C. (Box 2)
  - Randall, Alice R. (Box 2)
  - Raymond, Mary C. (Box 2)
  - Rice, Nancy Elizabeth (Box 2)
  - Schoonmaker, Anna Augusta (Box 2)
  - Skeel, Adelaide (Box 2)
  - Smith, Myra A. (Box 2)
  - Swift, Elma D. (Box 2)
  - Swinburne, Harriet K. (Box 2)
  - Swinburne, Virginia S. (Box 2)
  - Taylor, Mariposa (Box 2)
  - Thomas, Lilla S. (Box 2)
  - Townsend, Julia Gale (Box 2)
  - Townsend, Margaret Gibbons (Box 2)
  - Walker, Charlotte E. (Box 2)
  - Waller, Freelove E. (Box 2)
  - Weed, Mary Cornelia (Box 2)
  - Welch, Zelinda L. (Box 2)
  - Whitney, Adaline S. (Box 2)
  - Wilder, Blanche (Box 2)
  - Willard, Mary Adams (Box 2)
  - Wilson, Clara J. (Box 2)
  - Wing, Clara Angeline (Box 2)
- Class of 1874
  - Arnold, Helen (Box 2)
  - Barrett, Elizabeth W. (Box 2)
  - Bennett, Julia S. (Box 2)
  - Bird, Caroline A. (Box 2)
  - Boyd, Mary (Box 2)
  - Brown, Anne C. (Box 2)
  - Brown, Mary A. (Box 2)
  - Brownell, Laura H. (Box 2)
  - Chubb, Evangeline (Box 2)
  - Cushing, Florence M. (Box 2)
  - Cutter, Agnes E. (Box 2)
  - DeLand, Leora Adelaide (Box 2)
  - Dinsmoor, Florence A. (Box 2)
  - Eells, Helen Little (Box 2)
  - Ely, Harriett L. (Box 2)
  - Epler, Nellie Frances (Box 2)
  - Farnham, Annette E. (Box 2)
  - Fisher, Frances (Box 2)
  - Gilbert, Virginia B. (Box 2)
  - Hamlen, Elizabeth L. (Box 2)
  - Hamlin, Sarah A. (Box 2)
  - Hastings, Alice O'Brion (Box 2)
  - Hill, Elizabeth A. (Box 2)
  - Howes, Annie G. (Box 2)
  - Hoyt, Emma L. (Box 2)
  - Iredell, Annie Maria (Box 2)
  - Jackson, Helen G. (Box 2)
  - Jacobs, Miriam Owen (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Carrie E. (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Lucy Abby (Box 2)
  - Lionberger, Marion Scott (Box 2)
  - Livermore, Caroline (Box 2)
  - Mason, Josephine Marsh (Box 2)
  - McMillan, Lydia J. (Box 2)
  - Meeker, Anna L. (Box 2)
  - Mershon, Fannie Rowena (Box 2)
  - Munroe, Hannah Eveline (Box 2)
  - Ohlen, Harriett E. (Box 2)
  - Pomeroy, Amanda (Box 2)
  - Rea, Mary Lillie (Box 2)
  - Reed, Annie M. (Box 2)
  - Rollinson, Frances T. (Box 2)
  - Sanford, Pauline (Box 2)
  - Shouse, Fannie (Box 2)
  - Smiley, Pamelia Tarbell (Box 2)
  - Stillman, Charlotte E. (Box 2)
  - Stow, Lucretia A. (Box 2)
  - Thum, Pattie P. (Box 2)
  - Thurston, Annie Lucy (Box 2)
  - Trowbridge, Ella (Box 2)
  - Tuttle, Mary Rosanna (Box 2)
  - Watres, Carrie Gertrude (Box 2)
  - White, Emily I. (Box 2)
- Class of 1875
  - Alston, Nancy (Box 3)
  - Barton, Susannah C. (Box 3)
  - Bell, Margaret W. (Box 3)
  - Berry, Kate Louise (Box 3)
  - Bowen, Mary Elizabeth (Box 3)
  - Clark, Elizabeth K. (Box 3)
  - Clark, Emma K. (Box 3)
  - Connor, Lucia H. (Box 3)
  - Cotton, Ella N. (Box 3)
  - Crosman, Abbie M. (Box 3)
  - Cummings, Ada B. (Box 3)
  - Derrom, Mary Louisa (Box 3)
  - Farrar, Ellen W. (Box 3)
  - Gildersleeve, Lillie Adele (Box 3)
  - Gouldy, Jennie A. (Box 3)
  - Gourlie, Eliza Connor (Box 3)
  - Graham, Alice L. (Box 3)
  - Griffin, Ida Catharine (Box 3)
  - Hollister, Emma b. (Box 3)
  - Hower, Flora Alice (Box 3)
  - Jewell, Josephine M. (Box 3)
  - Kelley, Sarah J. (Box 3)
  - Kellogg, Lucy W. (Box 3)
  - Kiersted, Mary Augusta (Box 3)
  - Lewis, Lillie (Box 3)
  - Lough, Helen (Box 3)
  - Loverin, Clifford F. (Box 3)
  - Lyman, Katherine T. (Box 3)
  - Maltby, Katherine L. (Box 3)
  - Millard, Minna W. (Box 3)
  - Mitchell, Alice M. (Box 3)
  - Morss, Anna J. (Box 3)
  - Nelson, Laura (Box 3)
  - Northrop Ida (Box 3)
  - Parrish, Eleanor H. (Box 3)
  - Patchen, Lydia Mary (Box 3)
  - Pease, Julia M. (Box 3)
  - Perkins, Florence C. (Box 3)
  - Prudden, Lillian E. (Box 3)
  - Rumsey, Juliette Kinzie (Box 3)
  - Savage, Elizabeth D. (Box 3)
  - Seidel, Ella A. (Box 3)
  - Sellers, Lucy (Box 3)
  - Seys, Mary Ellen (Box 3)
  - Shotwell, Lillie Hallett (Box 3)
  - Skinner, Nancy (Box 3)
  - Storm, Margaret A. (Box 3)
  - Swift, Frances G. (Box 3)
  - Talcott, Sarah W. (Box 3)
  - Tappan, Eva M. (Box 3)
  - Taylor, Mary B. (Box 3)
  - Wait, Mary F. (Box 3)
  - Warren, Emily Amelia (Box 3)
  - Wheat, Florence C. (Box 3)
  - White, Cornelia F. (Box 3)
- Class of 1876
  - Adams, Mary L. (Box 3)
  - Ayrault, Emily Lawrence (Box 3)
  - Bell, Alice Morton (Box 3)
  - Biglow, Kate E. (Box 3)
  - Case, Henrietta (Box 3)
  - Castle, Julia A. (Box 3)
  - Chamberlain, Elizabeth (Box 3)
  - Clark, Martha (Box 3)
  - Clemson, Maria Amelia (Box 3)
  - Dickey, Sally Eugenia (Box 3)
  - Dodge, Ella (Box 3)
  - Dreer, Augusta N. (Box 3)
  - Fisher, Cynthia H. (Box 3)
  - Fleming, Sarah (Box 3)
  - Fox, Elizabeth R. (Box 3)
  - Gates, Sarah M. (Box 3)
  - Gifford, Elizabeth M. (Box 3)
  - Godfrey, Lillie Boker (Box 3)
  - Hale, Katharine T. (Box 3)
  - Hansell, Caroline (Box 3)
  - Harrison, Cora (Box 3)
  - Hersey, Heloise E. (Box 3)
  - Hileman, Jeannette (Box 3)
  - Hileman, Sallie (Box 3)
  - Hoagland, Merica Evans (Box 3)
  - Holton, Gertrude l. (Box 3)
  - Houliston, Esther M. (Box 3)
  - Hulburd, Alice L. (Box 3)
  - Jackson, Emma Caroline (Box 3)
  - Jacoby, Lillian (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Anna M. (Box 3)
  - Jordan, Mary A. (Box 3)
  - Keffer, Bertha (Box 3)
  - Knox, Lizzie S. (Box 3)
  - Large, Nora A. (Box 3)
  - Learned, Grace H. (Box 3)
  - Macomber, Jennie (Box 3)
  - Mangam, Laura M. (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Helen (Box 3)
  - Metcalf, Eliza G. (Box 3)
  - Morgan, Clara A. (Box 3)
  - Penfield, Annie F. (Box 3)
  - Perkins, Carrie (Box 3)
  - Poppleton, Ellen E. (Box 3)
  - Pratt, Helen C. (Box 3)
  - Price, Jeanie (Box 3)
  - Rankin, Abby M. (Box 3)
  - Richards, Emily S. (Box 3)
  - Richmond, Mary R. (Box 3)
  - Robinson, Mary B. (Box 3)
  - Roe, Anna M. (Box 3)
  - Rumsey, Elizabeth T. (Box 3)
  - Rutter, Harriet Louise (Box 3)
  - Scott, Mary A. (Box 3)
  - Shirk, Rosamond V. (Box 3)
  - Stanton, Margaret L. (Box 3)
  - Tolman, Julia (Box 3)
  - Tucker, Florence E. (Box 3)
  - Vinton, Elizabeth S. (Box 3)
  - Ward, Adelaide (Box 3)
  - White, Mabel T. (Box 3)
  - Wilkinson, Katha (Box 3)
- Class of 1877
  - Adams, Frances A. (Box 3)
  - Bliss, L. Adella (Box 3)
  - Brockway, Adelaide Emma (Box 3)
  - Castle, Mary H. (Box 3)
  - Chandler, Ada E. (Box 3)
  - Chisholm, Catherine A. (Box 3)
  - Cronin, Caroline Helen (Box 3)
  - Culbertson, Emma B. (Box 3)
  - Dana, Abby H. (Box 3)
  - Grant, S. Wilhemina (Box 3)
  - Gray, Lillie P. (Box 3)
  - Heller, Lida Kate (Box 3)
  - Hunter, Laura B. (Box 3)
  - Jamison, Jane (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Anna H. (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Charlotte LeB. (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Stells Medora (Box 3)
  - Latham, Josephine Bacon (Box 3)
  - Leach, Mary E. (Box 3)
  - Logan, Emma M. (Box 3)
  - Loomis, Eleanor G. (Box 3)
  - McKeaugue, Italia (Box 3)
  - Miller, Susan A. (Box 3)
  - Nuttman, Mary E. (Box 3)
  - Ogden, Harriet (Box 3)
  - Place, Mary Isabel (Box 3)
  - Rexford, Elizabeth M. (Box 3)
  - Rickards, Virginia (Box 3)
  - Rumsey, Ada W. (Box 3)
  - Shaw, Margaret M. (Box 3)
  - Sheppard, Sara F. (Box 3)
  - Smith, Meta Maria (Box 3)
  - Spallding, Mary T. (Box 3)
  - Stanton, Katherine L. (Box 3)
  - Stevens, Cornelia A. (Box 3)
  - Stone, Alice Amanda (Box 3)
  - Stoyell, Mary (Box 3)
  - Sutro, Emma L. (Box 3)
  - Swan, Frances W. (Box 3)
  - Swift, Caroline P. (Box 3)
  - Temple, Mary B. (Box 3)
  - Watson, Sarah D. (Box 3)
  - Webb, Ella C. (Box 3)
  - Wentworth, Anna Lewis (Box 3)
  - Whipple, Mary (Box 3)
  - Withington, Katherine (Box 3)
  - Wood, Ida (Box 3)
  - Woodward, Jessie M. (Box 3)
  - O'Leary, Helene B. (Box 3)
  - Thaw, Mary (Box 3)
- Class of 1878
  - Abbott, Mary M. (Box 3)
  - Barcalow, Anna Voorhees (Box 3)
  - Bascom, Gertrude (Box 3)
  - Beattie, Elizabeth (Box 3)
  - Bliss, Harriet Emily (Box 3)
  - Bond, Lillie T. (Box 3)
  - Botsford, Mary R. (Box 3)
  - Brown, Helen Dawes (Box 3)
  - Brown, Laura H. (Box 3)
  - Clarke, Mary W. (Box 3)
  - Cutler, Isabel (Box 3)
  - Davis, Jennie E. (Box 3)
  - Davis, Jessie M. (Box 3)
  - Day, Sarah L. (Box 3)
  - Dickey, Sarah J. (Box 3)
  - Dike, Francis Lowe (Box 3)
  - Elkins, Eleanor Blanche (Box 3)
  - Fullick, ELizabeth (Box 3)
  - Gaston, Mary E. (Box 3)
  - Gray, Lillie J. (Box 3)
  - Harlan, Antoinette B. (Box 3)
  - Hill, Mary S. (Box 3)
  - Hilliard, Martha (Box 3)
  - Howard, Grace Ellen (Box 3)
  - Hubbard, Mary T. (Box 3)
  - Innis, Martha (Box 3)
  - Ives, Marie E. (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Margaret Newsonm (Box 3)
  - Ketcham, Janie Merrill (Box 3)
  - Knowles, Grace Raymond (Box 3)
  - Littlefield, Fanny A. (Box 3)
  - McCaleb, Ella (Box 3)
  - Nelson, Isabel (Box 3)
  - Pidgeon, Annie E. (Box 3)
  - Pierson, Margaret H. (Box 3)
  - Putnam, Helen C. (Box 3)
  - Rainey, A. Sarah (Box 3)
  - Ransom, Harriot R. (Box 3)
  - Ray, Lydia P. (Box 3)
  - Rollins, Mary H. (Box 3)
  - Root, Mary P. (Box 3)
  - Rountree, Jennie Roberta (Box 3)
  - Shutt, Harriet V. (Box 3)
  - Stanton, Harriot E. (Box 3)
  - Thompson, Helen E. (Box 3)
  - Wardle, Elinor K. (Box 3)
  - White, M. Adeline (Box 3)
  - Whitman, Marie A. (Box 3)
  - Wing, Alice M. (Box 3)
- Class of 1879
  - Anderson, Nathalie S. (Box 4)
  - Baird, Marie F. (Box 4)
  - Banfield, Helen F. (Box 4)
  - Barr, Laura M. (Box 4)
  - Bellinger, Charlotte E. (Box 4)
  - Bentley, Eliza H. (Box 4)
  - Benton, Louise (Box 4)
  - Blake, Sallie T. (Box 4)
  - Bond, Mary R. (Box 4)
  - Braden, Nannie (Box 4)
  - Burch, Mary B. (Box 4)
  - Butler, Mary Marshall (Box 4)
  - Cady, Mary R. B. (Box 4)
  - Carver, Helen Ashley (Box 4)
  - Clarke, Eleanor P. (Box 4)
  - Cohn, Dora (Box 4)
  - Colgate, Mary (Box 4)
  - Cone, Elisabeth Morse (Box 4)
  - Cookingham, Mary E. (Box 4)
  - Cuddeback, Blandina M. (Box 4)
  - Dike, Cornelia A. (Box 4)
  - Dill, Jane L. (Box 4)
  - Durfee, Dora (Box 4)
  - Dutton, Anna Southmayde (Box 4)
  - Evans, Susie J. (Box 4)
  - Fletcher, Elizabeth E. (Box 4)
  - Forsyth, Katharine B. (Box 4)
  - Hakes, Mary E. (Box 4)
  - Hayes, Abby c. (Box 4)
  - Hazard, Bertha (Box 4)
  - Heck, Marianne (Box 4)
  - Hunt, Stella Fleming (Box 4)
  - Jacobson, Ethel (Box 4)
  - Jeffords, Minnie E. (Box 4)
  - Johnson, Carrie Leonard (Box 4)
  - Jordan, Emily C. (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, Susan D. (Box 4)
  - Merrick, Bertha V. (Box 4)
  - Moore, Ella R. (Box 4)
  - Moore, Lulu L. (Box 4)
  - Morey, Nettie D. (Box 4)
  - Negley, Sallie M. (Box 4)
  - Nichols, Sophia M. (Box 4)
  - Palmer, Gertrude (Box 4)
  - Perkins, Emma M. (Box 4)
  - Richardson, Sophia F. (Box 4)
  - Sharpe, Nannie G. (Box 4)
  - Simonds, Maria Rosette (Box 4)
  - Smith, Emma Almira (Box 4)
  - Starr, Marion E. (Box 4)
  - Tallman, Katherine Eliot (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Lillian Bayard (Box 4)
  - Teel, Jessie B. (Box 4)
  - Towner, Elizabeth W. (Box 4)
  - Turner, Anne M. (Box 4)
  - Wentworth, Sarah E. (Box 4)
  - Wickes, Martha Herriman (Box 4)
- Class of 1880
  - Aldrich, Katherine E. (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Hyla C. (Box 4)
  - Bailey, Annie P. (Box 4)
  - Gibson, Mrs. Robert J. (Box 4)
  - Barnes, Mariette A. (Box 4)
  - Beringer, Hattie C. (Box 4)
  - Blake, Josephine D. (Box 4)
  - Brewster, Jessie (Box 4)
  - Brockway, Louise L. (Box 4)
  - Canfield, Caroline M. (Box 4)
  - Cone, Jessica G. (Box 4)
  - Coryell, Sarah (Box 4)
  - Dickey, Mary irvine (Box 4)
  - Dow, Caroline B. (Box 4)
  - Drake, JeannieC. (Box 4)
  - DuBois, Jessie E. (Box 4)
  - Hartmann, Emma C. (Box 4)
  - Healy, Madge (Box 4)
  - Hendrick, Helen W. (Box 4)
  - Homes, Mary Louise (Box 4)
  - Hoyt, Mary F. (Box 4)
  - Hussey, A. Helen (Box 4)
  - Jeffords, Corrie Susan (Box 4)
  - Klahr, Emma (Box 4)
  - Lathrop, Julia C. (Box 4)
  - Martin, Lillien J. (Box 4)
  - McFadden, Anna C. (Box 4)
  - Morris, Mary S. (Box 4)
  - Murphy, Kate E. (Box 4)
  - Olmstead, Mary (Box 4)
  - Osterhout, Florence May (Box 4)
  - Parry, Angenette (Box 4)
  - Perkins, Carrie D. (Box 4)
  - Pratt, Lydia R. (Box 4)
  - Pratt, Mabel E. (Box 4)
  - Preston, Nellie J. (Box 4)
  - Reeve, Mary Allen (Box 4)
  - Reynolds, Myra A. (Box 4)
  - Rustin, Claire (Box 4)
  - Skinner, Elizabeth A. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Jessie F. (Box 4)
  - Street, Ida M. (Box 4)
  - Sutliff, Phebe T. (Box 4)
  - Swan, H. Rachel (Box 4)
  - Tappan, Lucy (Box 4)
  - Thurnauer, Sallie (Box 4)
  - Thurston, Ada (Box 4)
  - Tunnicliff, Mary Eliza (Box 4)
  - Van Allen, Anna (Box 4)
  - Van Kleeck, Adelaide (Box 4)
  - Walker, Carrie P. (Box 4)
  - Walker, Sarah Ann (Box 4)
  - Wardle, Anna (Box 4)
  - Wentworth, Emma B. (Box 4)
  - Wetzel, Ida A. (Box 4)